【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 2]
[第2集]
【Astrology Center】
【占星馆】
please.
请。
After you.
您先请。
【Astrology Center】
【占星馆】
Miss, please.
小姐，请。
What do the numbers in this passage mean?
这段话中的数字是什么意思？
Today our young master
今天我们的少爷
some of you will be chosen
将选择你们中的一些人
and divines for whomever he chooses .
并为他所选择的人占卜 。
One number per person. Keep it safe.
每人一个号码。好好保存。
So many people, there is a chance to be called
这么多人，有机会被叫到
They must be small, right?
它们一定很小，对吧？
When the sun rises from the earth,
当太阳从地球升起时，
Affects all sentient beings.
影响一切众生。
[Star Pavilion] All living beings are prosperous.
【星阁】 众生皆欣欣向荣。
The sun sets on the earth.
太阳落在地球上。
We enter the world of Yin.
我们进入阴的世界。
In autumn, yin and yang compete.
秋季，阴阳相争。
In winter, Yang Qi is hidden in stronger Yin Qi.
冬季，阳气隐藏在较强的阴气之中。
When the long night ends, the sun rises again.
当长夜结束，太阳再次升起。
The south represents light.
南方代表光明。
Everything is visible.
一切事物都是可见的。
She is the embodiment of the South.
她是南方的体现。
Excellent!
出色的！
touching.
感人的。
- Do you understand it? - Missed.
- 你明白了吗？ - 错过。
Are you here because of Star Catcher?
你是因为捕星大师才来的吧？
as you know?
如你所知？
girls who come here
来到这里的女孩们
10 out of 10
十分之十
They are waiting for him here.
他们在这里等他。
I assume you have this flyer too, don't you?
我想你也有这张传单，不是吗？
Let me tell you, the most popular image of the capital city
我来告诉你，最流行的首都形象
I gave it to you.
是我给的。
a woman like you
像你这样的女人
is their favorite.
是他们最喜欢的。
women like me
像我这样的女人
hatred.
恨。
You have high standards.
你有很高的标准。
Long life, happiness and joy.
长寿、幸福、快乐。
Excellent.
出色的。
This is my unpublished work.
这是我未发表的作品。
Very collectible.
极具收藏价值。
You will definitely thank me after reading it.
你看完后一定会感谢我的。
Thank you now.
现在谢谢你了。
-Are you disparaging my painting skills? - Never.
- 你是在贬低我的绘画技巧吗？ - 决不。
I gave it to you for free, but you refused.
我免费送给你，但你拒绝了。
As Mr. Xiaoyao, I am the best painter.
作为逍遥先生，我是最好的画家。
- But I feel humiliated. - shut up!
- 但我感到羞辱。 - 住口！
The ninth prophecy is that there will be no war on the border.
第九个预言，边境不会发生战争。
The tenth hexagram means peace and prosperity for the country and the people.
第十卦，国泰民安。
Excellent.
出色的。
- what is that? -you all think
- 那是什么？ -你们都认为
que a Rong Yu
que a Rong Yu
Is he a fairy?
是仙人吗？
Clear.
清除。
I believe he will eat.
我相信他会吃东西。
He Himself chooses the gods.
他亲自选择诸神。
- I suggest you change your career tomorrow. - Why?
- 我建议你明天改变你的职业。 - 为什么？
Because today I will make him the butt of a joke.
因为今天我会让他成为笑柄。
The astrology center will send the results to your home tomorrow.
明天占星馆 会把结果送到你家。
Why do we have to wait until tomorrow?
为什么我们要等到明天呢？
What?
什么？
Who is that? what is she doing?
那是谁？她在做什么？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
- Where is that person? - Yes.
- 那个人呢？ - 是的。
I've never seen him before.
我以前从未见过他。
Could it be that the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion cannot
难道 星象阁少主无法
Need someone else?
需要别人吗？
or maybe
或者可能
You need time to investigate them
你需要时间去调查他们
Forge and invent some riddles?
伪造和发明一些谜语？
Who are you and why are you making all this fuss?
你是谁，为什么要大惊小怪？
do not be afraid.
不要害怕。
Why be afraid?
为什么要害怕？
I did nothing.
我什么也没做。
what is she doing?
她在做什么？
Could it be that Jialin people
难道嘉林人
Can't you speak publicly these days?
这几天不能公开讲话吗？
What a disappointment.
真是令人失望。
all good.
都好。
Everyone is back.
大家都回来了。
miss.
错过。
Waiting for tomorrow doesn't suit me,
等待明天不适合我，
someone's fate, fortune, disaster
某人的命运、财富、灾难
It should only be known to that person.
它应该只有该人知道。
If I can't reveal it publicly
如果我不能公开透露的话
Why is everyone sitting here for nothing?
为什么大家都白白坐在这里？
Who says no one wants to
谁说大家都不想
Reveal your riddle to everyone?
向大家揭晓你的谜语？
I want everyone to
我愿意让大家
Look at my fate.
看看我的命运。
What? What's wrong?
什么？怎么了？
I learned that the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
我得知星象阁少主
Very talented.
非常有才华。
stop hiding
停止隐藏
and tell me my destiny
并告诉我我的命运
Show it to everyone.
给大家看。
- about what? - No guesswork if you are not selected.
- 关于什么？ - 如果您没有被选中，则无需猜测。
this is the rule
这是规则
Annual Astrology Festival.
每年的占星节。
This cannot be broken with just one sentence.
这不是一句话就能打破的。
And if everyone
而如果每个人
Ask the young master
问少爷
Practicing divination?
练习占卜？
Exactly.
确切地。
- Why does she need that? - and.
- 她为什么需要那个？ - 和。
She doesn't even know the rules.
她连规矩都不知道。
Simple.
简单。
- You, how could you do this? - How could she do this?
- 你，你怎么能这么做？ - 她怎么能这么做？
- She's a troublemaker. - Did she just catch them?
- 她是个麻烦制造者。 - 她刚刚抓住了它们吗？
Leave this outside the rules.
把这个放在规则之外。
- What? - I follow the rules.
- 什么？ - 我遵守规则。
No. 48.
48号。
No. 48, is anyone there?
48号，有人吗？
- who is it? - No. 48. Not us, right?
- 是谁？ - 48号。不是我们，对吧？
Number 48, right? here.
48号，对吧？这里。
it's me. I can't believe I was chosen.
是我。我不敢相信我被选中了。
look at me.
看着我。
Who is number 48?
48号是谁？
He, he, he, gemendo.
他，他，他，gemendo。
very good.
非常好。
it's me.
是我。
They groaned.
他们呻吟着。
I just follow the rules, don't I?
我只是遵守规则，不是吗？
all good. you did it!
都好。你做到了！
And me?
和我？
Who else wants to claim 48?
还有谁想索赔48？
If so, please move forward.
如果是这样，请向前迈进。
It seems I am the chosen one.
看来我是被选中的人了。
So please, Master.
那么拜托了，少爷。
Miss He, what do you want to diagnose?
何小姐，您想诊断什么？
This is my wedding destination.
这是我的婚礼目的地。
Okay, please.
好吧，拜托。
Madam, please tell us your date of birth.
小姐，请告诉我们您的出生日期。
In the sixth year of Zhenyuan,
贞元六年，
December 22nd.
12 月 22 日。
There's another knock on the door. She's always like this.
又在敲门了。她总是这样。
Look at her.
看着她。
Why didn't you say anything?
你为什么不说什么？
What's the prognosis?
预后如何？
Is it necessary to read so much?
有必要看那么多吗？
Can not you see?
你看不到吗？
The proficiency level of the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
星象阁少主的熟练程度
more or less.
或多或少。
What is the difference between you and those who are chasing fame and wealth ?
你和追名逐利的人有什么区别 ？
This makes me question the quality of your astrology studio.
这让我对你们星象馆的水平产生了质疑。
Don't say stupid things.
不要说傻话。
What did I say wrong?
我说错了什么？
I've seen the results.
我已经看到结果了。
Although,
虽然，
Multiple sclerosis. He, can you let me confirm again?
多发性硬化症。他，你能再让我确认一下吗？
As?
作为？
I'm so self-righteous
我真是太自以为是了
But miss. Can he get close to the tent?
但是小姐。他能靠近帐篷吗？
Let me touch the top of your head?
让我摸你的头顶？
Clear.
清除。
Why do I smell Phalaenopsis?
为什么我闻到蝴蝶兰的味道？
forget.
忘记。
if you tell the truth
如果你说实话的话
The fate of our marriage was not good;
我们的婚姻命运并不好，
I'll let her go.
我会让她走。
if you dare to use me
如果你敢利用我
Say something nice,
说一些好话，
I will make you a star-catching master
我会让你成为 摘星大师
Falling apart today.
今天分崩离析。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
sorry.
对不起。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
you know me.
你了解我。
Although we haven't officially met yet,
虽然我们还没有正式见面，
I think you should know
我想你应该知道
Why am I here.
为什么我在这里。
Run quickly.
快跑。
here. hide.
这里。隐藏。
good life.
美好生活。
Come, Prince Zheng
来吧，郑王爷
Let's get out of here.
我们离开这里吧。
He made a big fuss in the capital,
他在京城大闹，
——Don’t you know there is a He family? -Heshan.
——你不知道有一个何家吗？ -鹤山。
Master.
少爷。
Master, look.
少爷你看。
- let's break up. - Yes.
- 我们分手吧。 - 是的。
【Astrology Center】
【占星馆】
Pessigam separated.
佩西加姆分开了。
What about the horse?
那匹马呢？
- Who are you? ——He family, from the capital.
- 你是谁？ ——贺家，来自京城。
How dare you be so presumptuous?
你怎么敢如此放肆？
nonsense.
废话。
Bro, wait, wait.
兄弟，等等，等等。
Don't go away now.
现在别走开。
You are that man!
你就是那个男人！
I know.
我知道。
Although Xingxiang Pavilion is very famous, there,
尽管星象阁 很有名，在那里，
Shangzhou’s sister
商州的妹妹
It's so nice and virtuous.
真是太好了，有德行。
How could you change your loyalties so quickly?
你怎么能这么快改变你的忠诚？
Where is your conscience?
你的良心呢？
Sister, do you still remember our agreement yesterday?
姐姐，你还记得我们昨天的约定吗？
Next time we meet, you should.
下次我们见面时，你应该。
Make up for the massage you deserve.
补偿应有的按摩。
Did something happen to my sister?
是不是姐姐出了什么事情？
No.
不。
I know. You have no heart.
我知道。你没有心。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
- You you you - take them with you.
- 你 你 你 - 带上他们
I don't even want to talk to you.
我什至不想和你说话。
Take your broken sword.
拿走你断掉的剑。
You are afraid of me.
你怕我。
that's right.
这是正确的。
as you can see today
正如你今天看到的
and have heard in the past:
并在过去听到过：
I, He Jiuling, am a fierce general.
我何九龄，是一名猛将。
I have a bad temper and am not very kind.
我的脾气比较暴躁，也不是很善良。
So, what do you think of the fate of our marriage?
那么，你觉得我们的婚姻命运如何呢？
groom.
马夫。
Silta. Hey,
斯尔塔。嘿，
Why do you always abuse my young master?
为什么你总是虐待我少爷？
always?
总是？
You've adapted well to your new owner, haven't you?
你已经很适应你的新主人了，不是吗？
Why did I bully him?
我怎么欺负他了？
I didn't even touch it.
我什至没有碰它。
Since I started practicing martial arts, how many young people have I hurt?
自从我习武以来， 我伤害过的年轻人有多少
There can be a queue of more than 800 meters.
可以排起800多米的队列。
What is your young master's position?
你少爷是什么职位？
also,
此外，
I guard the arrow for you,
我为你守护箭，
I'll also help you catch the bad guys.
我还帮你抓坏人。
Have you forgotten everything?
你是不是已经忘记了一切？
This agenda
本次议程
He saved me when the lady was left behind.
当女士被留下时 他救了我。
If you keep it with you,
如果你一直带着它，
It must be very valuable.
它一定非常有价值。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
How can such a vulgar pamphlet be used?
这么低俗的小册子怎么能用？
Fantasy about my young master?
幻想我少爷？
- No! ——Stay away from the young master.
- 不！ ——离少爷远点。
Even if it can be done in the future
就算将来可以
Not today.
今天不行。
No, someone gave it to me for free.
不，有人免费给了我。
It's not free.
它不是免费的。
They forced me to use it.
他们强迫我使用它。
Anyway, I don't see any page.
无论如何，我没有看到任何页面。
Don't get me wrong.
不要误解我。
I see.
我明白。
great.
伟大的。
If it's not precious, why are you carrying it?
如果它不珍贵，你为什么要带着它？
I've already said it.
我已经说过了。
Now,
现在，
Someone put it on me in the hallway.
走廊里有人把它戴在我身上。
What a coincidence.
真是巧合啊。
- You... - Flatten!
- 你... - 展平！
Anyway, I'll find a place to burn it later.
无论如何，我稍后会找个地方烧掉它。
keep Calm.
保持冷静。
As for marriage,
至于婚姻，
If you find it difficult to speak,
如果你觉得说话很困难，
I see.
我明白。
We seemed to be on the same page.
我们似乎意见一致。
I'll wait for you at my house.
我会在我家等你。
The sooner we address this issue, the better. You need to hurry up.
我们越早解决这个问题越好。 你需要快点。
It has been sent to the Ministry of Punishment.
已经送到刑部了。
my brother works there
我哥哥在那里工作
and will look into it for you.
并将为您调查。
Let's break up here. I'm going home first.
我们就在这里分手吧。我先回家了。
His wound was still bleeding.
他的伤口还在流血。
I'll be scared if this continues.
如果再这样下去我会害怕的。
But all the medical clinics around
但周围所有的医疗诊所
Will be investigated by government soldiers.
将接受政府士兵的调查。
Let's consider another solution.
让我们考虑另一个解决方案。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
I must kill him.
我必须杀了他。
Master.
少爷。
He looked worried.
他看起来很担心。
Multiple sclerosis. Isn't he very good?
多发性硬化症。他不是很好吗？
I didn't see her marital destiny.
我没有看到她的婚姻命运。
why not?
为什么不？
After all, she is your fiancée, isn't she?
毕竟，她是你的未婚妻，不是吗？
because i saw
因为我看到了
Four years later,
那四年后，
She will die in Jialin.
她会死在嘉林。
How can this be?
这怎么可能？
When the previous owner arranged the wedding,
前任主人安排婚礼时，
He doesn't understand?
他不明白？
Her fate is strange.
她的命运很奇特。
It's just that they couldn't find it on her birthday, which is normal.
只是在她生日那天他们查不到，这也是很正常的。
Even I could only vaguely discern it.
就连我也只能隐隐约约地辨别出来。
If Miss He only has four years left to live,
如果何小姐只剩下四年的生命，
Master, isn't it?
少爷，不是吗？
Like a wizard,
就像巫师一样，
we see signs
我们看到迹象
and images
和图像
Not to fulfill destiny
不是为了完成命运
but fight another way
但以另一种方式战斗
Get rid of this fate.
摆脱这样的命运吧。
The children of the aristocracy were born into poverty.
贵族子弟出身贫寒。
Patients must fight to survive.
患者必须为生存而战。
In view of extreme circumstances,
鉴于极端情况，
They need to endure a lot of pain to survive.
他们需要承受很多痛苦才能生存。
people are not
人们不是
Have you been fighting against your destiny all your life?
一生都在与自己的命运作斗争吗？
Master,
少爷，
Exactly. I'm very happy.
确切地。我很开心。
Exactly.
确切地。
Do you understand it? I'm very happy.
你明白了吗？我很开心。
Even though the journey is difficult,
纵然路途艰辛，
I must change her fate
我必须改变她的命运
Against nature.
违背自然。
Jiuling, it looks like you've caused a stir.
九菱，看来你引起了轰动。
Yesterday at the Astrology Festival.
昨天在占星节上。
No wonder Rong Mansion sent someone here early in the morning.
难怪容府一 早就派人来了。
It can't wait.
它已经等不及了。
- Serious? ——Yes, as soon as Mr. Rong arrives,
- 严肃的？ ——是啊，荣爷一到，
I'll run to call you.
我跑去给你打电话。
Yesterday was worth grabbing.
昨天值得抓住。
Get up and get dressed.
起身穿好衣服。
Rong Yu looks like a weakling
容羽看上去就是个弱者
But it works quickly.
但作用很快。
Yes, after all, you are Rong Yu’s fiancée
是的，毕竟你是容羽的未婚妻
More than ten years.
十多年来。
Mr. Rong should compensate more.
荣爷应该多补偿一些。
We can't lose.
我们不能输。
- quickly. - correct.
- 快速地。 - 正确的。
What did you say?
你说什么？
How did this happen?
这怎么发生的？
A Rong Yu se feriu?
A Rong Yu se feriu?
Fortunately, Rong Yu was not injured.
幸运的是，容羽没有受伤。
but i heard
但我听说
The Cheng family wants revenge.
程家想要报仇。
Are you talking about Chengji?
你说的是成吉吗？
brazen.
厚颜无耻。
This is a family of thieves and prostitutes.
这是一个小偷和妓女的家庭。
If Rong Yu hadn't discovered
如果容羽没有发现
The location of the 30 million silver emergency fund,
3000万白银紧急资金的所在地，
I'm afraid the Cheng family
恐怕程家
Rumors will still be spread.
仍会散布谣言。
Talking about the Silver Caravan
话说银色商队
Washed away by floods.
被洪水冲走了。
They destroyed the victims' money
他们毁掉了灾民的钱
Carrying the emperor on his back.
背着皇帝。
it's a huge shame
这是一个巨大的耻辱
Punish them for their hard work at the border.
惩罚他们在边境的辛勤工作。
They dared to come back from the northwest to take revenge.
他们敢从西北回来报仇。
recently...
最近...
Even mice dare to challenge cats.
连老鼠都敢挑战猫。
If it weren't for the emperor's mercy
如果不是皇帝的仁慈
There won't be anything like yesterday.
就不会有昨天的事了。
Something important happened yesterday.
昨天发生了一件重要的事情。
I wish I could go with you.
我希望我能和你一起走。
Today, I brought some gifts to express my gratitude.
今天，我带了一些礼物 来表达我的谢意。
If he hadn't been beaten
如果不是挨打的话
Those people had already killed Rong Yu
那些人早就杀了容羽
and escaped without a trace.
并逃得无影无踪。
I can't stay here
我不能留在这里
And talk calmly.
并平静地交谈。
wrinkle
弄皱
Indeed, she is a blessed girl.
确实，她是一个有福气的女孩。
She is a lucky girl.
她是一个幸运的女孩。
But I'm a little confused.
但我有点困惑。
I heard that everyone is riding a Rong Yu horse
听说大家都骑着 容羽马
Almost ran off the bridge
差点跑下桥
But the horse fell.
但马却摔倒了。
I must say
我必须说
A bit fishy.
有点可疑。
it's me.
是我。
We have guests at home, why are you still here?
我们家里有客人，你怎么还在这儿？
I'm thinking about horses, right?
我在想马，对吗？
I'm the one who designed it.
我是设计它的人。
what have you done?
你做了什么？
I achieved a small success.
我取得了一个小小的成就。
I'm a little excited.
我有点兴奋。
Say it quickly.
说快点。
I have been insisting
我一直坚持着
Give He Jiuling the medicine
喂贺九龄的药
Every day, he is a war horse for Rongfu.
每日为 荣府战马。
As a result, the horses become weak and lethargic.
因此，马匹变得虚弱昏昏欲睡。
Fainted at the critical moment.
关键时刻晕倒。
That's true.
那是真实的。
What do you feed your horse? explain.
你给马喂了什么？说。
I love you.
我爱你。
General He, don't be angry.
何将军，您别生气。
- Are you crazy? - I'm going to take the spring exam, right?
- 你疯了？ - 我要去参加春季考试，对吗？
I want someone to give me recognition for what I do.
我希望有人对我所做的事情给予我认可。
I think I appreciate the gift too little.
我认为我 作为礼物的感激之情太少了。
After lunch in the afternoon, I will send someone there.
下午吃完午饭，我就派人去。
I don't deserve your praise.
我不值得你夸奖。
I really don't deserve it.
我实在不值得。
Since we agreed
既然我们同意了
About important issues.
关于重要问题。
I am going home.
我要回家了。
Please take a look
请看一下
On the engagement gift list.
在订婚礼物清单上。
Our astrology center will send them
我们占星馆会送他们
When calculating the best day of the month.
在计算该月最好的日子时。
What about the engagement day?
那么订婚日呢？
- You decide. - all good.
- 你决定。 - 都好。
Isn't he here to fulfill the engagement?
他不是来完成婚约的吗？
Why are you here?
你怎么也在这里？
How messy your hair is!
头发多乱啊！
what are you doing here? go.
你在这里做什么？去。
Volt.
伏尔特。
Teacher Rong, please forgive me for the way I educate my daughter.
荣老师，请原谅我对 女儿的教育方式。
I am so embarrassed.
我很尴尬。
A Rong Yu calculou
A Rong Yu calculou
And our astrological compatibility is not good either.
而且我们的星象兼容性也不好。
Father, I found you.
父亲，我找到你了。
- you! - We have to cancel the wedding!
- 你！ - 我们必须取消婚礼！
Rong Yu didn't tell me anything.
容宇没有告诉我任何事情。
He must have forgotten.
他一定是忘记了。
But if I tell you, it’s worth it too.
但如果我告诉你，这也是值得的。
Do you understand it?
你明白了吗？
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
you.
你。
How dare you hide from me?
你怎么敢躲着我？
You are terrible.
你太可怕了。
Today I will teach you a lesson
今天我就给大家上一课
You are rebellious!
你叛逆！
- You will see! - General, don't act without thinking.
- 你会看见！ - 将军，不要不假思索地行动。
If it is really Rong Yu's plan,
如果真是容羽算计的话，
He won't hide it from me.
他不会向我隐瞒的。
As for the general's visit this time , it was to discuss the wedding.
至于这次将军来访 是为了谈婚礼，
he mentioned
他提到
"That lady?" he asked fiercely yesterday.
“那位小姐？”昨天他激烈地问道。
I didn't ask.
我没有问。
How can I get him to propose to her?
我怎样才能让他向她求婚呢？
As for marriage,
至于婚姻，
If you find it difficult to speak,
如果你觉得说话很困难，
I see.
我明白。
We seemed to be on the same page.
我们似乎意见一致。
I'll wait for you at my house.
我会在我家等你。
The sooner we address this issue, the better.
我们越早解决这个问题越好。
You need to hurry up.
你需要快点。
drug.
药品。
A misunderstanding.
一个误会。
This must be a misunderstanding
这一定是一场误会
Misunderstand?
误会？
He didn't lose, he saw everything
他没有输，他看到了一切
Pretending to cause trouble at the Astrology Festival
假装在占星节上捣乱
To attract these killers
为了吸引这些杀手
confusion
混乱
and forget their own safety
并忘记自己的安全
And save Rong Yu?
并拯救容羽？
I think
我想
You care about him.
你很关心他。
Miss He, don't worry.
何小姐，别担心。
I won't let Rong Yu hurt you.
我不会让容羽伤害你。
Mr. Rong, this is a huge misunderstanding.
荣先生，这是一个天大的误会。
I didn't pretend to cause trouble.
我没有假装惹麻烦。
really good.
真的很好。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
still have a question.
还有一个问题。
you are wearing
你正穿着
a capa da Rong Yu?
a capa da Rong Yu?
- very good. - This cover
- 非常好。 - 这个封面
It is made from the fur of the snowy mountain silver fox.
它是由雪山银狐的毛皮制成的。
In addition to being extremely rare and expensive,
除了极其稀有和昂贵之外，
And it was a fox that the emperor personally hunted
而且还是皇帝亲自猎杀的狐狸
e dada à Rong Yu.
e dada à Rong Yu.
I wouldn't recognize her.
我不会认出她的。
I don't know what to say.
我不知道要说什么。
I'll give you anything you need
我会给你任何你需要的东西
But why would you steal other people's clothes?
但你为什么要偷别人的衣服呢？
you.
你。
group.
派。
I didn't steal.
我没有偷。
A Rong Yu me fez mal.
A Rong Yu me fez mal.
Enough nonsense.
废话够多了。
I'm leaving now.
现在我要走了。
Mr. Rong.
荣先生。
please don't misunderstand
请不要误会
What my daughter just said.
我女儿刚才说的话。
I will discipline my children
我会管教我的孩子
So I won't bother you.
所以我不会打扰你。
Clear.
清除。
miss. He has a kind heart.
错过。他有一颗善良的心。
General He, don't blame her too much.
贺将军，你别太责怪她了。
I will withdraw.
我会撤回。
please.
请。
- Zong Ming, - Sim.
- Zong Ming, - Sim.
- Escort Mr. Rong to the door. - Yes Master.
- 护送荣先生到门口。 - 是的主人。
Mr. Rong.
荣先生。
Silly girl!
傻丫头！
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Dare to hide.
敢于隐藏。
Stop hiding.
别再躲了。
What a silly girl!
真是个傻姑娘啊！
- Don't run. - Dad, this is a misunderstanding.
- 别跑。 - 爸爸，这是一个误会。
Dad, this is a misunderstanding.
爸爸，这是一场误会。
come over.
过来。
Kneel down.
跪下。
Stop protecting her!
别再保护她了！
- Dad - Do you still want to cover for her?
- 爸爸 - 你还要替她掩护吗？
- Don't run. - calm.
- 别跑。 - 冷静的。
- stop. - It hurts.
- 停止。 - 很疼。
- Silly girl. - Stop there.
- 愚蠢的女孩。 - 停在那儿。
Better to run.
最好是跑步。
- Run quickly. - stop.
- 赶紧跑。 - 停止。
It seemed like a scream. it seems
似乎是一声尖叫。它似乎
- Mercy. - shut up.
- 怜悯。 - 住口。
Dad is ruthless.
爸爸是无情的。
Think about it carefully,
好好想想，
After returning from Wuhua Mountain
从五华山回来后
It's been almost two months.
已经快两个月了。
I have more for you
我为你准备了更多
More in these two months than in the past 16 years.
这两个月比过去16年多。
look. here.
看。这里。
here and here.
这里和这里。
a man who has never been defeated
一个从来没有被打败过的人
Not a real man.
不能算是一个真正的男人。
This makes sense.
这说得通。
hope
希望
I'm going to take the spring exam soon
我马上就要参加春季考试了
I can't break my leg now.
我现在不能打断腿。
Then
然后
What are you going to do now?
你现在要做什么？
I'm looking for a way.
我正在寻找方法。
Judging from his appearance,
从他的外表来看，
When he looked at me, his eyes were wide.
当他看着我时，他的眼睛睁得大大的。
He is afraid of me.
他很怕我。
I don't think he is
我不认为他是
Trying to marry me.
试图嫁给我。
Am I wrong?
我错了没有
It's obvious that I hate him.
明显表明我讨厌他
Now there is a misunderstanding.
现在有一个误会。
How did he get it wrong?
他是怎么搞错的，
We need to talk.
我们需要好好谈谈。
if you go talk to him
如果你去跟他说话
What do you use a knife for?
你用刀做什么？
just kidding.
只是在开玩笑。
【Planetarium】
【天文馆】
What does Ms. mean? He wrote that he made her so happy?
Ms. 是什么意思？他写道他让她如此幸福？
She wants to see me.
她想见我。
You have to go.
你得走了。
In the two months since I returned to the capital,
回到首都的两个月里，
You and Heshan
你和鹤山
They are cleaning up something caused by the lady. Hey.
他们正在清理由女士造成的事情。嘿。
Just once, Heshan failed to act in time
就一次，鹤山没有及时行动
Mr. Song reported everything to the government.
宋先生将一切都向府里汇报了。
E o old man. He San,
E o 老先生。何三,
Climbing walls for no reason.
无缘无故地爬墙。
You need to talk reason into her head.
你需要向她的头脑中讲道理。
[Para Rong Yu]
[Para Rong Yu]
You have a lot to do every day
每天你都有很多事情要做
But you still need to pay attention to her.
但你还是需要关注她。
What's more, she saved me from danger a few days ago.
更何况前几天她还把我从危险中救了出来。
It's my duty to protect her.
保护她是我的责任。
if i can do this in my life
如果我能做到这一生
let her remain innocent
让她保持无辜
I will be very happy.
我会很开心。
Why must she change?
为什么她一定要改变？
It's hard for you and Heshan.
你和鹤山都很难。
We are not afraid of hard work,
我们不怕辛苦，
As long as we can help them.
只要我们能帮助他们。
I will pack an outfit for the date.
我会为约会准备一套衣服。
The Emperor sent new gifts from the Silk Pavilion a few days ago.
皇上 前几日从绸亭送来了新的礼物。
no need.
没有必要。
Our engagement is not yet complete.
我们的订婚尚未完成。
A private meeting would ruin her reputation.
一次私人会面会毁了她的名誉。
she doesn't understand
她不明白
But I have to behave.
但我必须表现得好。
When I went to Shangzhou last time,
上次去商州的时候，
I've offended her too much.
我已经得罪她太多了。
I can't make another mistake this time.
这次我不能再犯错误了。
She is known as the Overlord of the Capital.
她被称为京城霸王。
But she is still an innocent girl.
但她仍然是一个天真无邪的女孩。
Master, I care about you.
主人，关心的是你。
Avoiding me again.
又躲着我了。
I know.
我知道。
He is afraid of me.
他很怕我。
look.
看。
maybe your letter
也许你的信
Too aggressive
太有攻击性了
Who is afraid to go out.
谁害怕出去。
Don't forget that idiot young master
别忘了那个白痴少爷
do lorde Zhongyong
do lorde Zhongyong
I was worried about your challenge letter not long ago.
不久前为你的挑战信而担心
But still dare not leave.
却依然不敢离开。
He took the bathroom to the bedroom.
他把浴室带到了卧室。
what are you waiting for?
你在等什么？
Send another letter.
再寄一封信。
He is a weakling who cannot fight.
他是一只无法战斗的弱鸡。
Why are you trying to scare him?
你为什么要吓唬他？
Be gentle this time
这次要温柔一点
And convince him a little bit.
并稍微说服他一下。
What? He is a man. Why should I do this?
什么？他是男人。我为什么要这么做？
Be kind.
善待。
let's go.
我们走吧。
As the saying goes: "The bright moon is in the willow tree"
俗话说： “明月在柳梢头”
Trading takes place after dark.
交易是在天黑后进行的。
See you on the bridge tomorrow night?
明天晚上在桥上见你吗？
merge?
合并？
Master Rong, I miss you and dream about you
容大师，我想你，梦见你
crazily
疯狂地
Would you do me the honor of making your acquaintance?
您能让我荣幸地认识您吗？
teacher.
老师。
There should be ten, right?
应该有十个吧？
I've sent ten letters, right?
我已经送了十封信了，对吗？
Isn't this too kind?
这不是太仁慈了吗？
I even perfumed the paper.
我什至给纸上了香水。
I used all my talents
我用尽了我所有的才华
Write clear invitation verses.
写出明确的邀请诗句。
Isn't this sincere enough?
这还不够真诚吗？
Maybe Master Rong really has something going on.
或许容大师 真的有事。
How busy does he have to be?
他要多忙才能不能
Go out and talk?
出去说话吗？
He always said he was looking at the stars.
他总是说他在看星星。
Look at the charts during the day and the stars at night.
白天看海图 ，晚上看星星。
I think he's just evading and making excuses.
我认为他只是在逃避和找借口。
He had no idea what would happen when I lost my cool.
他不知道当我失去冷静时会产生什么后果。
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
If the mountains don't come to me, I will.
如果山不来找我，我就会来。
If he doesn't come to me, I'll come to him.
如果他不来找我，我就来找他。
I must kill him today.
今天我必须杀了他。
Killing chickens behind the kitchen
厨房后面杀鸡
And prepare some soup for my dad.
并为我父亲准备一些汤。
Brother, are you here to see the horses too?
兄弟，你也是来看马的吗？
We're here to get the horses.
我们是来取马的。
After the young lady came back from Wuhua Mountain,
小姐从五华山回来后，
My father kept some fine horses from the Turks,
我父亲从土耳其人那里保留了一些好马，
Prepare them to give it to the Lord.
准备他们将其献给主。
Today they finally arrived.
今天他们终于到了。
group.
派。
I was wrong.
我错了。
I shouldn't ignore him.
我不应该忽视他。
However,
然而，
You and Qiu Ting were almost killed
你和秋婷差点杀了
The proud horse of the Rong family
荣家的汗马
Dad feels bad.
爸爸感觉很糟糕。
He planned to give the horses to the Rong family.
他打算把马匹送给 荣家。
What?
什么？
They are Turkish horses and can travel thousands of kilometers in a day.
它们是土耳其马，一天可以行驶数千公里。
Do you want Rong Yu to use them to pull the cart?
你们要让容羽 用他们来拉车吗？
Might as well leave it to He San.
还不如交给何三呢。
if they were no better than horses
如果它们不比马更好的话
We cannot send them as gifts.
我们不能将它们作为礼物发送。
All because of you.
全都是因为你。
Father and brother.
父亲兄弟。
what are they doing?
他们在做什么？
She looked angrier now.
她现在看起来更生气了。
nothing.
没什么。
It’s just that his father is planning to use Turkish horses to compensate Rong Yu
只是父亲准备 用土耳其马补偿容羽
It was originally yours and Jiuling's.
本来是你和九灵的。
- What? - Give him more feed, okay?
- 什么？ - 给他更多的饲料，好吗？
correct.
正确的。
He always wants others to believe him.
他总是希望别人相信他。
The Ministry of Justice approved it and he should be there tomorrow.
法务部批准了， 他明天应该到场。
Until the spring exam,
直到春季考试，
You will report to me daily and read documents.
你将每天向我汇报并阅读文件。
What?
什么？
look.
看。
Isn't this a scream?
这不是尖叫声吗？
Yes!
是的！
let's go. She is not calm.
我们走吧。她不平静。
here it is.
这里是。
Always times.
总是次。
Take a look.
看一看。
Look how shameless you are!
你看多无耻啊！
- correct! - What a abused girl!
- 正确的！ - 多么受虐待的女孩啊！
- keeps coming. - no problem.
- 不断涌来。 - 没问题。
I miss her.
我想她。
You and I must be very close too.
你和我一定也很亲密。
I miss you so much after not seeing you for a few days.
几天没见到你后，我非常想念你。
There must be a lot to say after reading the brochure.
看完宣传册一定有很多话要说。
We are soul mates, I don't need to pretend.
我们是灵魂伴侣，我不需要假装。
you and me?
你和我？
When did we become soulmates?
我们什么时候成为灵魂伴侣了？
When the Star Reacher is ambushed,
当摘星大师遭到伏击时，
How you jumped into the rainbow.
你是如何跳进彩虹的。
everyone in the capital
首都的所有人
They know about your unrequited love for him.
他们知道你对他的单恋。
I have seen many ups and downs
我见过很多风风雨雨
But I praise your affection.
但我赞美你的深情。
I haven’t solved the sensual painting yet.
我还没解决感性的画。
How dare you gossip about my feelings for Rong Yu?
你竟敢八卦 我对容羽的感情？
I'm going to beat you until you fail to speak!
我要打你，打到你失言为止！
OK,
好的，
even if i didn't say
即使我没说
These people will think the same thing.
这些人也会有同样的想法。
Is it that obvious?
有那么明显吗？
You know exactly what happened.
你很清楚发生了什么。
If you want to save someone, save them.
如果你想拯救某人，就拯救他们。
Why hugs and hugs?
为什么要拥抱和拥抱？
This is what happened.
这就是发生的事情。
You are really capable.
你真的很能干。
I want to know which woman in the world
我想知道世界上有哪个女人
He was unwilling to hold Master Rong in his arms.
不愿意将容少爷抱在怀里。
But you did it,
但你做到了，
And in front of a lot of people.
并且当着很多人的面。
That sight is so exciting
那景象是那么令人兴奋
I want to draw.
我想画的。
It's all full of love,
都是满满的爱意，
Cannot be hidden.
无法隐藏。
No.
不。
If you don't believe it, just let it be.
如果你不相信，那就随它去吧。
Now.
现在。
I need to talk to you about something else.
我需要和你谈谈另一件事。
Sensual paintings.
感性的画作。
Do you read so fast?
你读得这么快吗？
The next volume is not ready yet.
下一卷还没有准备好。
Wait a moment.
等一下。
The sale of these items is not allowed in the capital.
首都不允许出售这些东西。
Do you print or sell it?
你打印或出售它吗？
Confess quickly
快表白
Otherwise I will beat you.
不然我就打你。
I didn't design it and I didn't sell it.
我没有设计它，也没有出售它。
So what are you hiding?
那么你在隐藏什么？
anything.
任何事物。
This noise.
这噪音。
Is it a fingerprint?
是指纹吗？
It's not with me.
它不在我身边。
if you don't admit it
如果你不承认的话
- I'll let you see a judge! - No!
- 我会让你见见法官！ - 不！
That's unfair of you.
你这很不公平。
You read it, but you don't want anyone else to read it, do you?
你读了它，但不希望别人读它，是吗？
Moreover, Star Lord is not her husband.
而且，星主也不是她的丈夫。
Why are you so overprotective?
你为何如此过度保护？
If you talk nonsense again, I will beat you.
你再胡言乱语，我就打你。
here it is.
这里是。
elder brother.
哥哥。
♫ Dusk as the sun sets♫
♫ 夕阳西下的黄昏 ♫
♫I have traveled thousands of miles ♫
♫我行万里路 ♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 月光下演奏西塔琴 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 你默默转身 ，合上结婚簿♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫问天上有多少颗星星♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫我轻轻地弹奏西塔琴 等待像你这样的人♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫最终你 是我不可避免的命运♫